Vinette D. Gutierrez

Full Stack Web Development |Technology

CONTACT



699 John St. #213 Seattle, WA 98109



650-438-6853



vinette.gutierrez@gmail.com

PROFILE

Full stack web developer with 5 years of experience in operations based roles in tech companies seeking full time employment on a technical team.. University of Washington Bootcamp graduate with skill in HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Express.js, React.js, Node.js, progressive web apps, agile methodology, computer science, database theory, MongoDB, MySQL, Git.

EXPERIENCE

CUSTOMER SUCCESS MANAGER • MAR 2021 - PRESENT

GETINSPECTIFY.COM [SEATTLE, WA]

- Client management Maintains positive relationships between home sellers and inspectors through multiple CRM tools (Front, Slack, OpenPhone, Web App)
- Customer Success Delights customers with high quality customer support before, during and after inspections.
- Documentation Creates and documents team strategies and workflows, while providing feedback to team on areas of improvement

Customer Success Advocate II/Application Guide• MAR 2020- MAR 2021 Boundless Immigration [SEATTLE,WA]

- Analysis Collected and analyzed sensitive customer documents in order to guide customers through the creation
 of marriage based green card petitions (AOS, RoC, CPI) that meets USCIS standards.
- Point of Contact- Primary touchpoint between immigration attorneys, staff and customers through multiple communication channels Email: Front, Phone: Aircall, Internal Comm: Trello, Slack, Boundless Admin)
- Case Management Managed individual case pipeline of 30 customers, meeting SLAs, while working on Customer Success optimization projects in collaboration with team mates

Business Operations - Quality Assurance/JIRA • APR 2018 - MAR 2020 Rover.com [SEATTLE,WA]

- Auditing Audited CX tickets and communicated results in order to help drive continuous improvement
- Standard Operating Process Constructed and updated internal SOP's to improve work quality and frontline
 effectiveness. Maintained up to date knowledge of support standards, goals, expectations and procedures
- Customer Retention Effort Successfully led and organized customer retention efforts retaining 15% of top platform users
- JIRA proofing Documented and improved reported website issues/bugs with technical and engineering teams. Provided feedback to support teams on how to deliver technical information to customers in a digestible and delightful manner

Customer Support Coordinator • OCT 2015 - AUG 2018 Giftcard Zen/RetailMeNot.com [PHOENIX,AZ]

- Customer Support Provided excellent customer support through company email, phone and social media accounts
- Fraud Analysis Oversaw company fraud issues including chargeback disputes and user compliance
- Diversity & Inclusion -Participated and contributed in employee resource groups promoting minorities and women in tech careers

EDUCATION

CERTIFICATE- MAR 2021
UNIVERSITY OF WASHINGTON - SEATTLE, WA

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT CODING BOOTCAMP

BACHELOR OF FINE ARTS, DEC 2013

ACADEMY OF ART UNIVERSITY - SAN FRANCISCO, CA

SOUND DESIGN, MUSIC FOR VISUAL MEDIA

SKILLS

- WEB DEVELOPMENT
- Customer Success
- Audio Technology

- QUALITY ASSURANCE
- ADAPTABLE
- Quick Learner